Guide to the Cause Marketing Forum. Halo Awards Records, 2002-2012 and undated RL.11128
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Cause Marketing Forum. Halo Awards Records, 2002-2012 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Cause Marketing Forum.
RL.11128
82.0 Linear Feet
Professional organization founded in 2002 by David Hessekiel to promote business-nonprofit collaboration and corporate sponsorship of social service campaigns. Halo Awards were established in 2003 to celebrate notable cause marketing campaigns.le endeavors by businesses.
Arrangement
Organized chronologically.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
However, original audiovisual materials are closed until use copies can be produced.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Cause Marketing Forum. Halo Awards Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2014.
Collection Overview
Collection spans 2002-2012 and includes correspondence, entry forms, audiovisual materials, artifacts, written reports and other materials that document businesses entering the awards competitions for social service and humanitarian projects. Companies and charities represented include the American Cancer Society, American Red Cross, Boys and Girls Clubs, Children's Miracle Network, Ford, Kohl's, Komen Breast Cancer Foundation/Komen for the Cure, Macy's, Procter & Gamble, Target and Toys for Tots. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising -- United States -- History; Charities -- United States -- Management; Humanitarian assistance; Advertising -- Social aspects; Corporations -- Public relations; Cause Marketing Forum.
- 2003, 1
  - Cause Marketing Campaign, 2003; 1
    - Loew's Cineplex/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Spotlight on the Cure, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Loew's Cineplex/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Spotlight on the Cure, 2003 (Box OV2)
    - Georgia Pacific/Ronald McDonald House: Quilted Northern and Ronald McDonald House Charities, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Georgia Pacific (Angel Soft)/Multiple partners: Angel Soft Angels in Action, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Environmental/Animal, 2003; 2
    - Briggs & Stratton/National Wildlife Federation: National Mower Tune-Up Month, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Free Standing Insert Creative, 2003; 3
    - Procter & Gamble/Special Olympics: Inspire Greatness, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Health-Related Message, 2003; 4
    - American Heart Association: Pictures of Good Health, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Bayer (Aleve)/Arthritis Foundation: Arthritis Walk, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Oneonta (Starr Ranch)/Washington Apples: American as Apple Pie Scholarship Contest, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Procter & Gamble/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Awareness is Love/Prevenir es Querer, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Procter & Gamble (Crest)/Boys and Girls Clubs of America: Cavity-Free Zone, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Weather Channel: Rays Awareness Sun Safety Campaign, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Joint Message, 2003; 5
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop/International Association of Fire Chiefs/Fraternal Order of Police: Stuffed with Hugs, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Johnson & Johnson/National Safe Kids Week: Use Your Head, Wear a Helmet!, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Target/Tiger Woods Foundation: Start Something Youth Education Program, 2003; 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Multiple Categories, 2003; 6
    - Clorox (Fresh Step)/ASPCA: Safe Steps Home, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Ford/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Get Tied to the Cause, 2003; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Ford/National Center for Missing and Exploited Children: Commitment to Kids, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Lee Jeans/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Lee National Denim Day, 2003; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2003 (Box 3)
    - Mrs. Fields' Cookies/Leukemia and Lymphoma Society: Light the Night Walk, 2003 (Box OV1)
    - Mrs. Fields' Cookies/Leukemia and Lymphoma Society: Winning is Sweet...So Are the Days of Our Lives, 2003 (Box 3)
    - Samsung/Multiple partners: Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope, 2003; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Whole Foods/Share Our Strength: Chefs Upfront Series, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2003; 7
    - ConAgra Foods/Multiple partners: Feeding Children Better Initiative, 2003 (Box 3)
    - DisneyHand/First Book: Reading Together Program, 2003 (Box 3)
    - Domino's Pizza/Make a Wish Foundation: Domino's Delivers Incredible Wishes, 2003 (Box 3)
    - Elefanten Children's Shoes/Americans for the Arts: Steps to Art, 2003; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - J.C. Penney/Boys & Girls Clubs of America: Afterschool Programs, 2003; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Lee Jeans/LearningWorks: Lee Pipes Get in Gear Bike Safety Program, 2003 (Box 4)
    - Liz Claiborne: Women's Work Program, 2003; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Timberland/Share Our Strength: Crib Booties, 2003 (Box 4)
    - Verizon/Multiple partners: Verizon Reads, 2003; 3 folders (Box 5)
    - White Castle/Bread for the City: Bread for the City, Give and Let Live, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Whole Foods/Share Our Strength: Chefs Upfront Series, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Yahoo!/National Center for Missing and Exploited Children: Missing Kids Campaign, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Transactional, 2003; 8
    - Blockbuster/Boys & Girls Clubs of America: Kids' Club Summer Recess, 2003 (Box 5)
    - CIBC: Children's Miracle Day, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Cingular Wireless/Special Olympics of North America: Cingular/Special Olympics Partnership, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Finish Line/Boys & Girls Clubs of America: Give It Up for Kids, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Finish Line/Boys & Girls Clubs of America: Give It Up for Kids, 2003 (Box OV8)
    - KitchenAid/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Cook for the Cure, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Potawatomi Bingo Casino/Multiple partners: Miracle on Canal Street, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Procter & Gamble/UNICEF: Give Kids a Fresh and Caring Start, 2003 (Box 6)
    - R.H. Donnelly (Sprint Yellow Pages)/Multiple partners: Recycle for Literacy, 2003; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Walgreen/American Cancer Society: Hope Blooms with You, 2003 (Box 6)
    - Walgreen/American Cancer Society: Hope Blooms with You, 2003 (Box OV2)
    - Yoplait/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Destination Yoplait, 2003 (Box 6)
- 2004, 2
  - Environmental/Animal, 2004; 9
    - Microsoft/The Explorers Club: Central Park Bioblitz, 2004 (Box 6)
    - REI/YMCA: YMCA Earth Science Corps, 2004 (Box 6)
  - Event, 2004; 10
    - American Kennel Club: Responsible Dog Ownership Day, 2004; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - BMW of North America/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: The Ultimate Drive, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Cold Stone Creamery/Make a Wish: World's Largest Ice Cream Social, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Entemann's/New York Departmen of Parks and Recreation: Por un Barrio Mejor, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Entemann's/New York Departmen of Parks and Recreation: Por un Barrio Mejor, 2004 (Box OV8)
    - Just Born/Easter Seals: Marshmallow Peeps Fun Bus Tour, 2004 (Box 7)
    - KitchenAid/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Cook for the Cure, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Lowe's/America Red Cross: Racing for Relief, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Sephora: Operation Smile, 2004 (Box 7)
    - Target/NEA: Read Across America, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Health-Related Message, 2004; 11
    - March of Dimes: Prematurity Campaign, 2004; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - March of Dimes: Prematurity Campaign, 2004 (Box 8)
    - March of Dimes: Prematurity Campaign, 2004 (Box OV12)
    - Scholastic/Pennsylvania Department of Health: The Uninvited Guest, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Wyndham International/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Dream for the Cure, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Yoplait/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Save Lids to Save Lives/Yoplait Champions, 2004 (Box 8)
  - Joint Message, 2004; 12
    - ABC Radio Networks/U.S. Department of Health and Human Services: Closing the Health Gap, 2004; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Ford/National Park Foundation: Rosie the Riveter/World War II Home Front National Historical Park, 2004 (Box 8)
    - Ford/National Park Foundation: Rosie the Riveter/World War II Home Front National Historical Park, 2004 (Box 9)
    - Heifer International/Green Mountain Coffee Roasters: Heifer Hope Blend, Coffee for a Better World, 2004 (Box 9)
    - History Channel/Library of Congress and Smithsonian Institute: Save Our History, Save Our Sounds, 2004; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Hollywood Video/Starlight Children's Foundation: The Power of Entertainment, 2004; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Hollywood Video/Starlight Children's Foundation: The Power of Entertainment, 2004 (Box 10)
    - NexTel Communications/American Red Cross: Donate a Phone, 2004 (Box 10)
    - Pampered Chef/American Cancer Society: Let's Whip Cancer, 2004 (Box 10)
    - Schering-Plough/Scholastic/Sun Safety Alliance: Block the Sun, Not the Fun, 2004 (Box 10)
    - Target/Tiger Woods Foundation: Start Something Youth Education Program, 2004; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - UAW-GM and General Motors/Make a Wish Foundation: Make a Difference Day, 2004; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Multiple Categories, 2004; 13
    - Avon/American Legacy Foundation/Mark/Circle of Friends: Make Your Mark, Join the Circle, 2004 (Box 10)
    - Iowa Health System/Iowa Public Television: Healthy Kids Gang, 2004; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Iowa Health System/Iowa Public Television: Healthy Kids Gang, 2004 (Box OV4)
    - Keep America Beautiful: Great American Cleanup, 2004; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Kellogg (Special K)/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Keep the Promise with Kellogg's, 2004 (Box OV9)
    - Lowe's/Home Safety Council: The Great Safety Adventure, 2004; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Scholastic/Multiple nonprofits: ClassroomsCare, 2004 (Box OV6)
    - Stanley/Home Depot/SkillsUSA: Stanley and the Home Depot Salute SkillsUSA, 2004 (Box 11)
  - Print Creative, 2004; 14
    - Colgate-Palmolive/Starlight Children's Foundation: Creating Smiles, 2004 (Box 12)
    - Embassy Suites/Starlight Children's Foundation: Together, Imagine What We Can Do, 2004 (Box 12)
    - Embassy Suites/Starlight Children's Foundation: Together, Imagine What We Can Do, 2004 (Box OV10)
    - Embassy Suites/Starlight Children's Foundation: Together, Imagine What We Can Do (glass star in box), 2004 (Box OV13)
    - Finalists, 2004 (Box 12)
    - Ford/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Get Tied to the Cause, 2004 (Box 12)
    - Lee Jeans/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Lee National Denim Day, 2004 (Box 12)
    - Wishbone/Make a Wish Foundation: Natalie's Nalu Dressing, 2004; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2004; 15
    - Brooks Brothers/Make a Wish, 2004 (Box OV8)
    - History Channel/Library of Congress and Smithsonian Institute: Save Our History, Save Our Sounds, 2004; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Liz Claiborne: Women's Work Program, 2004; 4 folders (Box 13)
    - Parade Magazine/Share Our Strength: Great American Bake Sale, 2004 (Box 13)
    - Trend Magazine/Volunteer Florida Foundation: Teen Trendsetter Reading Mentors, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Trend Magazine/Volunteer Florida Foundation: Teen Trendsetter Reading Mentors, 2004 (Box OV10)
    - Universal Studios/First Book: Cat in the Hat Nationwide Challenge, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Verizon/Historically Black Colleges and Universities: Verizon HBCU Student Art Competition, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Verizon/Schools in the U.S.: Extra Credit for Schools, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Transactional, 2004; 16
    - American Airlines/USO: Flying High for the Troops, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Austin Grill: Austin Grill Alexandria First Monday Charity Night, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Blockbuster/Boys & Girls Clubs of America: National Kids Day, Kids' Club, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Brookstone/Save the Children: Give the Gift of Hope, 2004 (Box OV4)
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop: Nikki's Bear Campaign, 2004; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop: Nikki's Bear Campaign, 2004 (Box OV2)
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop: Nikki's Bear Campaign (bear voice module, ribbon pin), 2004 (Box OV11)
    - Colombo Yogurt/Adams National Historical Park: Preserve Our Heritage Campaign, 2004 (Box 14)
    - GlaxoSmithKline (Tum's)/First Responders Institute: Tums Helps Put Out More Fires than You Think, 2004 (Box OV6)
    - RCA Music Group (American Idol)/American National Red Cross: God Bless the USA/What the World Needs Now Is Love, 2004 (Box 14)
    - R.H. Donnelly (Sprint Yellow Pages)/Multiple partners: Recycle for Literacy, 2004 (Box 14)
    - Things Remembered/Make a Wish Foundation, 2004; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Things Remembered/Make a Wish Foundation--Waterglobe, star with stones, pewter heart, 2004 (Box OV13)
    - Walgreen/American Cancer Society: Hope Blooms with You, 2004 (Box 15)
- 2005, 3
  - Environmental/Animal, 2005; 17
    - MemberDrive/National Wildlife Foundation: Ranger Rick Endorsement, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Event, 2005; 18
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop/USO: Stuffed with Hugs, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Horizon Blue Cross and Blue Shield of New Jersey/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Race for the Cure Golf Classic, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Samsung/Multiple partners: Samsung's Four Seasons of Hope, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Sunkist/7-Eleven: Rock the Vote, 2005 (Box 15)
    - Sunkist/7-Eleven: Rock the Vote, 2005 (Box OV7)
    - Women's International Bowling Congress/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Bowl for the Cure, 2005 (Box OV11)
  - Health-Related Message, 2005; 19
    - National Philanthropic Trust/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Breast Cancer 3-Day, 2005; 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Scholastic/New Jersey Family Care: Keep Our Children Safe from Lead!, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Scholastic/New Jersey Family Care: Keep Our Children Safe from Lead!, 2005 (Box OV8)
    - U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention: VERB Anytour, 2005 (Box 16)
    - U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention: VERB Anytour (sock ball, tape ball, "anyhoop"), 2005 (Box OV13)
    - Wal-Mart/Produce for Better Health Foundation: 5 a Day the Color Way Retailtainment Educational Fairs, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Wal-Mart/Produce for Better Health Foundation: 5 a Day the Color Way Retailtainment Educational Fairs, 2005 (Box OV2)
    - Wal-Mart/Produce for Better Health Foundation: 5 a Day the Color Way Retailtainment Educational Fairs (Peanuts in-store display), 2005 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - Wal-Mart/Produce for Better Health Foundation: 5 a Day the Color Way Retailtainment Educational Fairs (includes Shrek in-store display), 2005 (Box OV10)
    - Wyndham International/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Dream for the Cure, 2005 (Box 16)
  - Joint Message, 2005; 20
    - Hershey Foods/Children's Miracle Network: Kissmobile Tour, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Hershey Foods/Children's Miracle Network: Kissmobile Tour, 2005 (Box OV2)
    - Hershey Foods/Children's Miracle Network: Kissmobile Tour, 2005 (Box OV12)
    - J.M. Family Enterprises/Big Brothers and Sisters: Fit to Play, 2005 (Box 16)
    - J.M. Family Enterprises/Big Brothers and Sisters: Fit to Play, 2005 (Box OV7)
    - Lady Footlocker/American Cancer Society: Breast Cancer Awareness, 2005 (Box OV4)
    - Lancôme USA/Girls Incorporated: Girls Inc. Corporate Camp, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Lancôme USA/Girls Incorporated: Girls Inc. Corporate Camp, 2005 (Box OV4)
    - Lockheed Martin/USO: Lockheed Martin Employees Care, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Regal Entertainment/Boys & Girls Clubs of America: Regal Free Family Film Festival, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Volkswagen/Scholastic: Fasten Your Seatbelts...Go Far!, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Volkswagen/Scholastic: Fasten Your Seatbelts...Go Far!, 2005 (Box OV1)
  - Multiple Categories, 2005; 21
    - 3M (Post-It)/City of Hope Cancer Center: Sticking Up for Breast Cancer Research, the World's Largest Pink Ribbon, 2005; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Axa Financial/Scholarship America: Axa Achievement, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Axa Financial/Scholarship America: Axa Achievement, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Axa Financial/Scholarship America: Axa Achievement, 2005 (Box OV1)
    - California Nutrition Coalition: Get Healthy California, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Georgia-Pacific (Quilted Northern)/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Quilts of Inspiration, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Kiehl's Since 1851/YouthAIDS: Wash with a Cause, 2005 (Box 18)
    - ProstateNet: The Barbershop Initiative, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Target/Tiger Woods Foundation: Start Something Youth Education Program, 2005; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Target/Tiger Woods Foundation: Start Something Youth Education Program, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Toys R Us/Marine Toys for Tots Foundation: Every Child Deserves a Toy at Christmas, 2005 (Box 19)
    - U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention: Niños activos, familias sanas, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Whirlpool/Habitat for Humanity: Key, 2005 (Box 19)
  - National/Local Integration, 2005; 22
    - Allstate/National Network to End Domestic Violence: Allstate Foundation Domestic Violence Program, 2005 (Box 19)
  - Print Creative, 2005; 23
    - Esquire Magazine/Cartier/Hollywood Entertainment Museum: Esquire's Cartier/Hollywood Entertainment Museum Special Advertising Section, 2005 (Box 19)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2005; 24
    - CitiCards/Scholastic: Writing and Scholarship Planning for College-Bound Students, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Coca-Cola/Albertson's/Reading Is Fundamental, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Doubletree Hotels: Teaching Kids to Care, 2005; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Greater L.A. County Vector Control District: Wipe Out West Nile Virus, 2005 (Box 20)
    - Heifer International: Read to Feed, 2005; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - HSBC: Your Credit Counts, 2005 (Box 20)
    - HSBC: Your Credit Counts, 2005 (Box OV2)
    - Multiple/Home Safety Council: Safety Ranger Spot Dangers, 2005 (Box 20)
    - NFL/Scholastic: One World, Connecting Communities, Cultures and Classrooms, 2005 (Box 20)
    - Pearson/Jumpstart: Pearson-Jumpstart Partnership, 2005 (Box 21)
    - PNC Financial/Multiple nonprofit: PNC Grow Up Great, 2005; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Samsung Electronics: Samsung's Hope for Education, 2005 (Box 21)
    - VH1 Save the Music Foundation, 2005 (Box 21)
    - VH1 Save the Music Foundation, 2005 (Box OV4)
    - Volkswagen/Scholastic: Develop Your Powers of Persuasion, 2005 (Box 21)
  - Transactional, 2005; 25
    - K-Mart/March of Dimes: K-Mart In-Store Paper Sneaker Promotion Benefitting March of Dimes, 2005 (Box 21)
    - Pier 1 Imports/Komen Breast Cancer Research Foundation: Pier 1 Komen Candle, 2005 (Box 21)
    - Procter & Gamble (Bounty)/Multiple nonprofit: Bounty Cards that Count, 2005 (Box 21)
    - Stop & Shop/Jimmy Fund of Dana-Farber Cancer Institute: Triple Winner Game, 2005; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Stop & Shop/Jimmy Fund of Dana-Farber Cancer Institute: Triple Winner Game poster, 2005 (Oversize-folder 2)
- 2006, 4
  - Environmental/Animal, 2006; 26
    - Animal Planet/National Wildlife Federation: Backyard Habitat TV series, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Animal Planet/National Wildlife Federation: Backyard Habitat TV series, 2006 (Box OV4)
    - AT&T/National Arbor Day Foundation: AT&T's MySBC eBill Paperless Program, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Ellen Degeneres Show/Wildlife Conservation Society: Going Once...Going Twice...Name that Monkey!, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Salt Lake Brewing Company/No More Homeless Pets in Utah: Chasing Tail Bottle Cap Program, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Sam's Club/Keep America Beautiful: Return the Warmth, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Sun Microsystems: Let's Change This, 2006 (Box 22)
  - Event, 2006; 27
    - Backpacker Magazine/Big City Mountaineers: Summit for Someone, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Clif Bar (Luna)/Breast Cancer Foundation: Lunafest, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Cold Stone Creamery/Make a Wish: World's Largest Ice Cream Social, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Hard Rock International/Chris Farley Foundation: Ambassadors of Rock Tour in New York, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Hyundai/CureSearch National Childhood Cancer Foundation: Hyundai Hope on Wheels, 2006; 3 folders (Box 23)
    - Lee Jeans/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Lee National Denim Day, 2006; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2006 (Box 23)
    - Multiple/Greater Chicago Food Depository: Hunder Knows No Season, 2006 (Box 23)
    - R.H. Donnelly (Sprint Yellow Pages)/Multiple partners: Recycle for Teachers, 2006 (Box 24)
    - Sam's Club/Keep America Beautiful: Great American Cleanup, 2006 (Box 24)
    - Space Needle (Seattle)/Habitat for Humanity: Tackling Hurricane Relief, 2006 (Box 24)
  - Health-Related, 2006; 28
    - Clif Bar (Luna)/Breast Cancer Foundation: Luna Spreading Awareness and Raising Money for the Breast Cancer Foundation, 2006; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2006 (Box 24)
    - Scholastic: Head's Up--Real News About Drugs and Your Body, 2006 (Box 24)
  - Joint Message, 2006; 29
    - Aldo/YouthAids/Population Services International: Hear No Evil, See No Evil, Speak No Evil, 2006 (Box 24)
    - Avon/Avon Foundation: Let's Talk Beauty Tour/Speak Out Against Domestic Violence, 2006 (Box 24)
    - Gibson Guitars/Musicares: Music Rising, 2006 (Box 25)
    - Gibson Guitars/Musicares: Music Rising, 2006 (Box OV8)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2006 (Box 25)
    - Music Matters/Organic Trade Association/Earth Day Network/Maccabee Group: Go Organic for Earth Day!, 2006 (Box 25)
    - ReMax/Children's Miracle Network: ReMax Premier Community Citizenship: Grace in Action, 2006; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Multiple Categories, 2006; 30
    - Coca-Cola/National Association of Collegiate Directors of Athletics (MACDA): Community All-Americans, 2006 (Box 25)
    - Coca-Cola/National Association of Collegiate Directors of Athletics (MACDA): Community All-Americans, 2006 (Box OV4)
    - Condé Nast Publications (Golf Digest)/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Rally for a Cure, 2006; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Ford/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Get Tied to the Cause, 2006 (Box 25)
    - Ford/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Get Tied to the Cause, 2006 (Box OV4)
    - Harrah's/Meals on Wheels: Mayors for Meals, 2006 (Box 25)
    - Jones Apparel Group: Jones NY in the Classroom, 2006; 2 folders (Box 26)
    - KitchenAid/Komen Breast Cancer Foundation: Cook for the Cure, 2006 (Box 26)
    - Non-finalist extras, 2006 (Box 26)
    - Procter & Gamble (Iams)/Multiple nonprofit: Home 4 the Holidays, 2006 (Box 26)
  - National/Local Integration, 2006; 31
    - Energizer/International Association of Fire Chiefs: Change Your Clock Change Your Battery, 2006 (Box 26)
    - Intercontinental Hotels/U.S. Fund for UNICEF: Designs of Hope, 2006 (Box 26)
    - J. C. Penney/Boys & Girls Clubs of America: Goals for Graduation Rally with Johnny Damon, 2006 (Box 26)
    - Luxaire Heating and Air Conditioning/Make-a-Wish Foundation: Delivering the Magic of a Wish, 2006 (Box 26)
    - Major League Baseball/Habitat for Humanity: MLB Rebuilds, 2006 (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2006 (Box 27)
    - Select Comfort/Ronald McDonald House: A Better Night's Sleep for Those in Need, 2006; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - UPS Store/Marine Toys for Tots Foundation: Deliver Some Love, 2006 (Box 27)
  - Print Creative, 2006; 32
    - Aldo/YouthAids/Population Services International: Hear No Evil, See No Evil, Speak No Evil, 2006 (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous entry forms, 2006 (Box 27)
    - Procter & Gamble/VH1 Save the Music Foundation: BrandSaver, 2006 (Box 27)
  - Social Service/Educational, 2006; 33
    - Avon/Avon Foundation: Let's Talk Beauty Tour/Speak Out Against Domestic Violence, 2006 (Box 27)
    - Cartoon Network/National PTA: Rescuing Recess, 2006 (Box 27)
    - Charles and Helen Schwab Foundation: Schwab Learning, 2006 (Box 27)